Robert E. Lee Papers WLU.Coll.0064
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
- Letters from Robert E. Lee, 1833-1870 (Box 1-4B)
  - Letters from Robert E. Lee, 1833-1862 (Box 1)
    - Robert E. Lee to Unknown Individual, 1862-03-03; Robert E. Lee expresses gratitude for the box of prepared meats sent to him. Relates the importance of "nutritious and palatable"in maintaining some comfort in camp life. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1862-03-14; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee updates his brother on his current professional commitment and expresses insecurity in his ability to fulfill his role properly. (Box 1, Folder 53)
      Lee, Charles Carter
    - Robert E. Lee to John H. Forney, 1862-04-02; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee notifies Forney of his promotion to Brigade General and instructs him to report for duty to General Sam Jones. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Robert E. Lee to A. L. Long, 1862-04-19; Robert E. Lee offers Long an appointment to be his secretary upon Senate confirmation and Long's acceptance. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Robert E. Lee to Thomas Jonathan "Stonewall" Jackson, 1862-04-25; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee notifies the general that it is too late for him to get a hold of an artist by the time Jackson requested. (Box 1, Folder 56)
      Jackson, Thomas Jonathan (Stonewall)
    - Robert E. Lee to James K. Caskie Esq., 1862-05-05; Robert E. Lee notifies Caskie that he may have an interview with the President later that afternoon. (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Robert E. Lee to Richard S. Ewell, 1862-05-08; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses possible troop movements. (Box 1, Folder 58)
      Ewell, Richard Stoddert, 1817-1872
    - Robert E. Lee to Henry T. Clark, 1862-05-18; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee attempts to rectify a miscommunication between the North Carolina governor and himself. (Box 1, Folder 59)
      This file only includes a facsimile of the document mentioned. Please refer to the owner of the original document for conditions governing use.
      Clark, Henry T. (Henry Toole), 1808-1874
    - Robert E. Lee to Joseph E. Johnston, 1862-05-19; Robert E. Lee informs the general that there are no troops in Richmond that suit his request. (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Robert E. Lee to George Wythe Randolph, 1862-06-16; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee ask Randolph to call his headquarters before riding into town. (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Robert E. Lee to George B. McClellan, 1862-07-12; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee informs McClellan that he has no objection receiving the baggage of his wounded and unwounded officers. (Box 1, Folder 62)
      McClellan, George Brinton
    - Robert E. Lee to Samuel Basset French, 1862-08-08; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee expresses regret because he has been unable to spend time with the troops. (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1862-08-24; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses strategic movements and his ability to feed the troops. (Box 1, Folder 64)
      Davis, Jefferson
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1862-08-30; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee shares a Confedersate victory with Davis. (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1862-09-03; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee writes to Jefferson Davis regarding the second Battle of Bull Run. (Box 1, Folder 66)
      Bull Run, 2nd Battle of, Va., 1862; Davis, Jefferson
    - Robert E. Lee to John D. Imboden, 62-10-06; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee commends the Colonel for his success at Hanging Rock. (Box 1, Folder 67)
      Imboden, John D. (John Daniel)
    - Robert E. Lee to W. N. Pendleton, 1862-10-10; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee advises which route Pendleton should take. (Box 1, Folder 68)
      Pendleton, William Nelson
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1862-11-06; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses strategy before the Battle of Fredericksburg. (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Robert E. Lee to Ambrose Everett Burnside, 1862-12-19; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses a private who was captured and will be tried as a spy. (Box 1, Folder 70)
      Burnside, Ambrose Everett
    - Robert E. Lee to William Fitzhugh Lee, 1853-02-02 (Box 1, Folder 18a)
    - Robert E. Lee to Margaret Elliot, 1853-07-12 (Box 1, Folder 25a)
  - Letters from Robert E. Lee, 1863-1865 (Box 2)
    - Robert E. Lee to Howell Cobb, 1863-01-12; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses the feasibility to shifting companies around. (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Robert E. Lee to John F. Skaggs, 1863-03-29; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Lee thanks Skaggs for sending a gift. (Box 2, Folder 72)
      This file only includes a photostatic copy of the original note. The location of the original document is unknown. Please refer to the owner of the original for conditions governing use.
    - Robert E. Lee to John D. Imboden, 1863-07-13; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee commands Imboden to cross the Potomac and stop the advance of the enemy. (Box 2, Folder 73)
      The file only includes a transcript of the note. Please refer to the owner of the original document with questions regarding conditions governing use.
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1863-08-22; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee replies to Davis' declining of his resignation after the Battle of Gettysburg. (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1863-09-03; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee informs Davis that the Florida brigade cannot be spared unless an equal force can be sent to take its place. (Box 2, Folder 75)
      This file includes a photostatic copy of the original note. Please refer to the owner with any questions regarding conditions governing use.
    - Robert E. Lee to George Washington Custis Lee, 1863-09-30; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee requests that his son take his valued watch to get repaired and send it back as soon as possible. (Box 2, Folder 76)
      Lee, George Washington Custis
    - Robert E. Lee to Gooch Raily, 1863-11-25; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee commends Raily for his commitment to the country, although he cannot advise him to act against the wishes of his parents. (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Robert E. Lee to Nat Burwell, 1863-12-14; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee thanks Burwell for sending apples and wild cat skin. (Box 2, Folder 78)
      This file only includes a photocopy of the original letter. Please refer to the owner of the original document with any questions regarding conditions governing use.
    - Robert E. Lee to Gooch Raily, 1863-12-19; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee expresses contentment at hearing that Raily will enter the service and serve the Confederacy. (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mary C. Jerdone, 1863-12-29; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee thanks Mary for sending him a handkerchief and a note. (Box 2, Folder 80)
      The file only includes a copy of the original note. Please refer to the owners of the original document for questions regarding the conditions governing use.
    - Robert E. Lee to Mary C. Jerdone, 1864-01-16; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee requests that Jerdone eat something and notifies her that he sent partridges. (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Robert E. Lee to Richard Stoddert Ewell, 1864-02-18; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee asks that Ewell address the many desertions. (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1864-02-20; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses the need for crops and bacon to feed the troops and discusses the death of his daughter-in-law Charlotte. Mentions other family matters and personal updates. (Box 2, Folder 83)
      This file only includes a photostatic copy of the original letter. Please refer to the owner of the documents with any questions regarding the conditions governing use.
    - Robert E. Lee to James Longstreet, 1864-03-08; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee writes on possible strategy for Tennessee campaign. (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1864-04-15; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); General Lee discusses general strategy, particularly in defense of Richmond, Virginia. (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Robert E. Lee to Armistead L. Long, 1864-04-16; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); General Lee expresses that the artillery of the 2nd Corps should advance to the front. (Box 2, Folder 86)
      Long, A. L. (Armistead Lindsay), 1827-1891
    - Robert E. Lee to James Longstreet, 1864-04-20; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); General Lee discusses present situtation at various locations. (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Robert E. Lee to Neilia Cave, 1864-04-21; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); General Lee thanks Cave for sending a gift and updates her on successes at Plymouth, North Carolina. (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1864-04-23; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Robert E. Lee discusses general strategy with Jefferson Davis. (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Letter, not by Lee, with accompanying note by Lee, 1864-04-26; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward) (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Robert E. Lee to Blair Robertson, 1864-04-30; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward) (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1864-07-07; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward) (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1864-08-04; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward) (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1864-08-12; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward) (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1864-08-13 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jubal A. Early, 1864-09-17 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Nelson Pendleton, 1864-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Robert E. Lee to Unknown, 1864-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Robert E. Lee to George E. Pickett, 1864-11-01 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Robert E. Lee to Briscoe Baldwin, 1864-11-18 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Robert E. Lee to James A. Seddon, 1864-12-24 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jubal A. Early, 1865-01-04 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mary C. Jerdoe, 1865-01-08 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Robert E. Lee to Samuel Cooper, 1865-01-10 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mrs. B. E. L. Wilfong, 1865-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Henry Fitzhugh Lee, 1865-02-04 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jefferson Davis, 1865-02-09 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles F. Suttle, 1865-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Robert E. Lee to Ulysses S. Grant, 1865-02-18 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Robert E. Lee to James Longstreet, 1865-02-22 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Robert E. Lee to Henry Heth, 1865-04-02 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Robert E. Lee to William D. Cabell, 1865-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Robert E. Lee to Armistead L. Long, 1865-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Robert E. Lee to Caroline Cora (Peters) Benson, 1865-07-22 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Robert E. Lee to William D. Cabell, 1865-07-27 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Robert E. Lee to R. H. Anderson, 1865-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Robert E. Lee to P. G. T. Beauregard, 1865-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Robert E. Lee to Walter H. Taylor, 1865-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Robert E. Lee to Butler C. Carter Lee, 1865-08-18 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Robert E. Lee to William D. Cabell, 1865-08-21 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Robert E. Lee to the Board of Trustees of Washington College, 1865-08-24 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Nelson Pendleton, 1865-08-28 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Robert E. Lee to James H. Caskie, 1865-08-30 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Robert E. Lee to Fitz Lee, 1865-09-01 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Robert E. Lee to G. A. White, 1865-09-18 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Robert E. Lee to Eli Metcalfe (E. M.) Bruce, 1865-09-25 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Robert E. Lee to P. G. T. Beauregard, 1865-10-03 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Robert E. Lee to Joseph S. Topham & Co., 1865-10-06 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Robert E. Lee to Edward A. Pollard, 1865-10-12 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Robert E. Lee to Joseph S. Topham, 1865-10-31 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Robert E. Lee to Alfred Rives, 1865-11-01 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Robert E. Lee to S. Vinser (?), 1865-11-02 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jubal Early, 1865-11-22 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Robert E. Lee to Robert Beverly, 1865-11-25 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Robert E. Lee to Cyrus McCormick, 1865-11-28 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Robert E. Lee to William M. Shaw, 1865-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Robert E. Lee to Henry Howard Gratz, 1865-12-11 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Robert E. Lee to Anna M. Fitzhugh, 1865-12-14 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mrs. M. B. Brown, 1865-12-28 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Letters from Robert E. Lee, 1866-1868 (Box 3)
    - Robert E. Lee to Samuel D. Stuart, 1866-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Robert E. Lee to Thomas Miller, 1866-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Robert E. Lee to Samuel D. Stuart, 1866-01-06 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Robert E. Lee to W. I. Hawks, 1866-01-08 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Robert E. Lee to Maggie M. Sawyer, 1866-01-18 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Robert E. Lee to George L. Baker, 1866-01-23 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Robert E. Lee to John W. Brockenbrough, 1866-01-23 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Robert E. Lee to James B. Dorman, 1866-01-23 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Robert E. Lee to Churchill Gibson, 1866-01-24 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mary Anna Morrison Jackson, 1866-01-25 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Robert E. Lee to Longstreet, Owens, and Co., 1866-01-26 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Robert E. Lee to James S. Ford, 1866-02-25 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Robert E. Lee to John B. Baldwin, 1866-02-26 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Robert E. Lee to Reuben Johnston, 1866-03-06 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jubal Early, 1866-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Robert E. Lee to Samuel D. Stuart, 1866-03-16 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Robert E. Lee to William J. Folkes, 1866-03-21 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Robert E. Lee to Edward L. Hedden, 1866-03-23 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jennie Congdon, 1866-04-10 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Robert E. Lee to Alexander Gardiner, 1866-04-25 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Robert E. Lee to Alexander Gardiner, 1866-05-19 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Robert E. Lee to James Longstreet, 1866-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Robert E. Lee to I. Lucian Jones, 1866-05-28 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Robert E. Lee to A. R. Hays, 1866-06-04 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Robert E. Lee to John B. Lapsley, 1866-06-05 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Robert E. Lee to Osman Latrobe, 1866-06-08 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Robert E. Lee to John R. Thompson, 1866-06-09 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Robert E. Lee to James K. Edmondson, 1866-06-29 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Robert E. Lee to J. W. Lapsley, 1866-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles S. Venable, 1866-07-06 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Robert E. Lee to Henry L. Tucker, 1866-07-18 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Robert E. Lee to James P. Rogers, 1866-07-21 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Robert E. Lee to Peregrine Wroth, 1866-08-11 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Robert E. Lee to Tardy, Williams, and Co., 1866-08-14 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Robert E. Lee to S. Bassett French, 1866-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Robert E. Lee to P. G. Sutphin, 1866-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Robert E. Lee to Frederick Gussetti, 1866-09-26 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Robert E. Lee to James L. Bewley, 1866-09-28 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Robert E. Lee to I. D. Driesbach, 1866-10-03 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Robert E. Lee to E. T. Bledsoe, 1866-10-08 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Robert E. Lee to Joseph Henry, 1866-10-13 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Robert E. Lee to Jubal Early, 1866-10-15 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Robert E. Lee to Socrates Maupin, 1866-10-17 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Marshall, 1866-11-09 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Robert E. Lee to Washington College Board of Trustees, 1866-11-16 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Robert E. Lee to James K. Edmondson, 1866-11-19 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Robert E. Lee to Duncan M. McIntyre, 1866-11-20 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Robert E. Lee to Students, 1866-11-26 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Robert E. Lee to Lord Acton, 1866-12-15 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Robert E. Lee to Educational Association of Virginia, 1866-12-31 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Robert E. Lee to John B. Minor, 1867-01-17 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Robert E. Lee to David S. G. Cabell, 1867-02-25 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1867-03-14 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Robert E. Lee to William B. Reed, 1867-03-21 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Robert E. Lee to James Chestnut, 1867-05-17 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Robert E. Lee to John C. Shafer, 1867-06-15 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Robert E. Lee to John L. Campbell, 1867-09-09 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Letter extending credit for college fees, 1867-09-23 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Robert E. Lee to T. F. Carter, 1867-09-26 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Robert E. Lee to W. W. Austin, 1867-09-30 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1867-10-24 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Robert E. Lee to Fitz John Porter, 1867-10-31 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Robert E. Lee to Hugh McCulloch, 1867-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Robert E. Lee to William "Billy" Mahone, 1867-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Robert E. Lee to James K. Edmondson, 1867-11-15 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Robert E. Lee to Andrew W. Varner, 1867-11-16 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Robert E. Lee to Martha Norvell Caskie, 1867-11-22 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mrs. S. R. Alexander, 1867-12-18 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Robert E. Lee to Miers W. Fisher, 1867-12-24 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Robert E. Lee to Richard Bland Lee, II, 1868-01-06 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Robert E. Lee to John B. Lafitte, 1868-01-13 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Robert E. Lee to William McLaughlin, 1868-01-27 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Robert E. Lee to Richard L. Page, 1868-02-10 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Nelson Pendleton, 1868-02-13 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Robert E. Lee to C. B. Richardson, 1868-02-28 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Robert E. Lee to Douglas Frazar, 1868-03-02 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Robert E. Lee to John W. Truslow, 1868-03-07 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Robert E. Lee to Rodney A. Mercer, 1868-03-26 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Robert E. Lee to Miss Lella, 1868-04-12 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Robert E. Lee to Walter Herron Taylor, 1868-04-13 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Robert E. Lee to William C. Rives, 1868-04-29 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Robert E. Lee to N. W. Hibbard, 1868-05-14 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Robert E. Lee to D. R. Osbourne, 1868-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Robert E. Lee to R. H. Maury, 1868-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Robert E. Lee to William G. Williamson, 1868-06-15 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Robert E. Lee to Edwin Gray Lee, 1868-06-22 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Robert E. Lee to Frank Alexander Waddill, 1868-06-25 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Marshall, 1868-07-02 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Robert E. Lee to Unknown, 1868-07-02 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Robert E. Lee to Robert Beverly, 1868-07-02 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Robert E. Lee to Julia Lee, 1868-07-06 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Robert E. Lee to E. C. Gordon, 1868-08-03 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Robert E. Lee to E. C. Gordon, 1868-08-18 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Robert E. Lee to E. C. Gordon, 1868-09-02 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Robert E. Lee to John F. Tackett, 1868-11-30 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - Robert E. Lee to W. A. Morgan, 1868-12-03 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Robert E. Lee to A. Minis, 1868-12-05 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1868-12-22 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - Robert E. Lee to H. I. Furber, 1868-12-23 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Robert E. Lee to J. Wilcox Brown, 1868-12-23 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Letters from Robert E. Lee, 1869-1870 (Box 4)
    - Robert E. Lee to to William G. Miller, 1869-01-05 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - Robert E. Lee to William P. Hoerton, 1869-01-08 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Nelson Pendleton, Col. J. T. L. Preston, and William White, 1869-01-11 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1869-01-15 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Robert E. Lee to Leon Nicely, 1869-01-19 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Robert E. Lee to Chester D. Hubbard, 1869-01-22 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1869-02-02 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Robert E. Lee to Henry I. Furber, 1869-02-08 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - Robert E. Lee to Nat Burwell, 1869-02-15 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Robert E. Lee to Hamilton S. Neale, 1869-02-23 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Robert E. Lee to Washington College Student Body, 1869-03-30 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mrs. F. S. Cater, 1869-04-02 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Robert E. Lee to Frank Barnett, 1869-05-10 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Robert E. Lee to S. G. Robinson, 1869-06-26 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Robert E. Lee to Lucius Desha, 1869-06-26 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Robert E. Lee to S. Lee, 1869-06-26 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Robert E. Lee to D. A. Deaderick, 1869-06-26 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Robert E. Lee to Williw Wilson Hobson, 1869-06-26 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Robert E. Lee to Joseph G. Steele, 1869-06-29 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Robert E. Lee to the Firm of Mason, Fenwick, and Lawrence, 1869-07-06 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1869-07-08 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Henry Ruffner, 1869-07-22 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Robert E. Lee to Dr. McConaughy, 1869-08-05 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Robert E. Lee to J. M. Leech, 1869-08-10 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Robert E. Lee to Charles Carter Lee, 1869-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Robert E. Lee to Mr. Woodward, 1869-08-29 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Robert E. Lee to Daniel Ruggles, 1869-09-03 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Robert E. Lee to Washington College Faculty and Staff, 1869-09-24 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Robert E. Lee to John Barron, Jr., 1869-11-18 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Robert E. Lee to A. C. Niven, 1869-11-24 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Henry Ruffner, 1869-11-30 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Robert E. Lee to Thomas H. Ellis, 1869-12-30 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Robert E. Lee to Miss Len Campbell, 1870-01-10 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Robert E. Lee to Augustus Robin, 1870-01-18 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Robert E. Lee to John W. Beckwith, 1870-01-20 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Robert E. Lee to Sidney Root, 1870-01-21 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Robert E. Lee to Nahum Capen, 1870-01-21 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Robert E. Lee to Fitz John Porter, 1870-02-05 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Robert E. Lee to Emily Hay, 1870-02-15 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Robert E. Lee to Fitz John Porter, 1870-02-18 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Robert E. Lee to Joseph Henry, 1870-03-11 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Robert E. Lee to William Preston Johnston, 1870-03-15 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Robert E. Lee to Ann L. Jones, 1870-03-16 (Box 4, Folder 282)